下一步，让我们来做一个练习
For the next step, let's do an exercise that focuses
来取出这些属性的其中一个的值
on extracting out the value of one of those attributes. We're
这次做练习的方式有点不同。你应该在
going to do this exercise a little bit differently. You'll implement this
Udacity平台上完成它。这样我们就能验证
on the Udacity platform. And we'll be able to verify that
你的代码是否正确。在这个视频结束后，你会看到一个像这样的IDE
your code is correct. After this video, you'll see an IDE
其中包含一些初始的代码
like this. Where it contains some starter code, as well as
旁边的标签页有一些Java单元测试（JUnit）代码
some j unit tests in a separate tab. In particular, we
我们希望你来实现这个函数，取得一天的最大温度
want you to implement this function, to get the max temperature
会给你一个JSON字符串，里面是天气数据
for a day. You're given a weather JSON
和之前从OpenWeatherMap服务端
string, formatted the same way as you would get
取得的JSON是一样的格式
from the Open Weather Map service. And you
另外你也会获得我们关注的那天的日期索引
also get the day index that we care about.
开动大脑来编写代码吧
Feel free to play around with the code
用Android Studio，或者其他开发环境
in Android Studio, or a separate development environment, before
之后将写好的代码粘贴到这儿。你也可以
you paste your answer here. Or you can use
直接用Udacity的IDE。如果你喜欢的话。
the Udacity IDE. Whichever feels more natural to you.